<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>How to use the Icon Pack?</item>
        <item>How to apply the Icon Pack?</item>
        <item>How to see all the included icons?</item>
        <item>How to replace certain icons with alternatives?</item>
        <item>How to request unthemed icons?</item>
        <item>After restarting my device, icon pack is not applied anymore. Icons were restored to
            default.
        </item>
        <item>Why do icons look pixelated on my device?</item>
        <item>I can see an icon for X app in the grid included icons, but the icon does not apply.
        </item>
        <!--
        <item>How to hide app icon from launcher?</item>
        -->
        <!-- -->
        <item>How to open the app after app icon is hidden from launcher?</item>
        <item>How to show launcher icon again?</item>
        <!-- -->
        <item>Why does the app need permission to modify or delete content of my storage?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to full network access?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to view connections?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to set wallpaper?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to adjust the wallpaper size?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to prevent phone from sleeping?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>You need a launcher with Icon Pack support.
            Check the Google Play Store description for supported launchers.
            If you are not sure which launcher should you use, just go to \"Apply\" section, then
            choose one from the list.
        </item>
        <item>Go back to main section of the app, then tap the Floating Action Button.
            Choose the launcher you want to apply the icons too.
            If your launcher is not listed there, but this icon pack is compatible with it
            (see on Google Play Store description for the list of supported launchers),
            you can apply it manually from launcher settings.
        </item>
        <item>Go back to main section of the app, then tap the card which title is \"Icons\".</item>
        <item>It depends on the launcher you are using. Not every launcher support icon editing.
            But, in most of them, you can edit the icon by long-pressing it or doing a double tap.
        </item>
        <item>Go back to main section of the app, then tap the card which title is \"Requests\".
        </item>
        <item>It happened because the icon pack was moved to SD Card, you should install it in
            internal storage.
        </item>
        <item>The problem might come with the launcher you are using, when handling big resolution.
            You can fix it by increasing icon size to 115 - 120%.
            Or try using another launcher.
        </item>
        <item>Send an icon request.</item>

        <!--
        <item>Some launchers support hiding icons. Check your launcher settings.</item>
        -->

        <!-- -->
        <item>Go back to main section of the app, then tap the card which title is \"Settings\".
            Then check the \"Hide icon from launcher\" option.
        </item>
        <item>Go to your homescreen, then create a shortcut widget for the app.</item>
        <item>Go back to main section of the app, then tap the card which title is \"Settings\".
            Then uncheck the \"Hide icon from launcher\" option.
        </item>

        <!-- -->
        <item>It\'s needed to be able write and read icon requests data and files.</item>
        <item>It\'s needed to be able to load the cloud based wallpapers and download them.</item>
        <item>It\'s needed to be able to check if your device has internet connection.</item>
        <item>It\'s needed to be able to apply wallpaper directly from the app.</item>
        <item>It\'s needed to be able to adjust wallpapers dmiensions based on your screen
            resolution.
        </item>
        <item>It\'s needed by Muzei Live Wallpaper.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
